[{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980258364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6846,"timeElapsed":68155},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980261428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3061,"timeElapsed":71219},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980265778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4346,"timeElapsed":75569},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980279454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":13673,"timeElapsed":89244},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980287257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7800,"timeElapsed":97048},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980294614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":7354,"timeElapsed":104405},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980299332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4715,"timeElapsed":109123},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7006,"timeElapsed":116133},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2803,"timeElapsed":118938},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":17413,"timeElapsed":137645},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3091,"timeElapsed":140738},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980334870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3921,"timeElapsed":144661},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980340695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5822,"timeElapsed":150485},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3807,"timeElapsed":154295},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3978,"timeElapsed":158277},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980351511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3023,"timeElapsed":161302},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2294,"timeElapsed":163598},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2763,"timeElapsed":166363},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980368221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":10483,"timeElapsed":178011},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2602,"timeElapsed":180616},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1914,"timeElapsed":182532},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980375863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3121,"timeElapsed":185654},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1940,"timeElapsed":187597},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980383264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5455,"timeElapsed":193055},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1663,"timeElapsed":194720},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4375,"timeElapsed":199097},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1649,"timeElapsed":200748},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6095,"timeElapsed":207898},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":211000},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4020,"timeElapsed":215022},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3492,"timeElapsed":218517},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1632,"timeElapsed":220150},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417529,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7168,"timeElapsed":227320},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4333,"timeElapsed":231656},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1398,"timeElapsed":233055},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4187,"timeElapsed":237245},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1461,"timeElapsed":238709},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4659,"timeElapsed":244340},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2014,"timeElapsed":246357},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2097,"timeElapsed":248456},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1834,"timeElapsed":250292},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1473,"timeElapsed":251767},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2276,"timeElapsed":254045},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1210,"timeElapsed":255258},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2689,"timeElapsed":257949},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980449525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1365,"timeElapsed":259316},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3375,"timeElapsed":263609},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1924,"timeElapsed":265535},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1970,"timeElapsed":267508},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":269708},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1548,"timeElapsed":271258},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1780,"timeElapsed":273041},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1540,"timeElapsed":274582},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":276294},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1851,"timeElapsed":278148},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8371,"timeElapsed":287406},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2964,"timeElapsed":290372},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1922,"timeElapsed":292296},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980485197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2690,"timeElapsed":294988},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1376,"timeElapsed":296366},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2199,"timeElapsed":298568},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1362,"timeElapsed":299932},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2378,"timeElapsed":302312},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4485,"timeElapsed":306799},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9314,"timeElapsed":317147},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510569,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3210,"timeElapsed":320359},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4378,"timeElapsed":324741},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1658,"timeElapsed":326401},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1970,"timeElapsed":328373},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1160,"timeElapsed":329535},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2276,"timeElapsed":331813},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1238,"timeElapsed":333054},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1904,"timeElapsed":334960},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1209,"timeElapsed":336171},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6829,"timeElapsed":343975},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2011,"timeElapsed":345987},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1338,"timeElapsed":347326},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2098,"timeElapsed":349426},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1126,"timeElapsed":350555},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2318,"timeElapsed":352876},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1186,"timeElapsed":354064},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1741,"timeElapsed":355808},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1084,"timeElapsed":356894},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":13319,"timeElapsed":371093},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":373510},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2562,"timeElapsed":376074},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980567889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1604,"timeElapsed":377680},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1083,"timeElapsed":378766},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1731,"timeElapsed":380499},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1336,"timeElapsed":381838},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1416,"timeElapsed":383256},{"subjectID":"r91suoxogu","prolificID":"63f8aeb6c9098e0ef3bf3553","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24e133f7fbc5db06753","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2362,"timeElapsed":385620}]